

# TONAVALENCIA

INTERACTIVE MEDIA DESIGN

tona.valencia@hotmail.com (+57) 304 590 2690 http://tonavalencia.github.io https://www.linkedin.com/in/ paula-valencia/

#### **LANGUAGES**



Spanish



English



Japanese

## **BASIC SKILLS**







### **DESIGN SKILLS**













### **SOCIAL SKILLS**

Excellent communication,
Adaptability, interpersonal
skills, teamwork, work under
pressure, time management
and leadership.

#### Personal Profile

My name is Paula Valencia I'm an Interactive Media Designer from Colombia. I describe myself as a curious person, someone who love to learn new things and my passion is to create, music and learning about new cultures. During my life, I have developed skills that make me able to work with User Experience, Graphic Design, Web Design, App Development, Video Editing and other aspects.

### **Achivements**

1st Place Icesi University Internal Archery Tournament 2014 4th place in contest of Japanese oratory 2015. Icesi University ISEP Scholarship 2016

## **Education**

Coomeva High School, June - 2013. Nihon University International Exchange, Japan. Feb 2017. Icesi University. Cali, Colombia. August - 2018 Current GPA 4.1/5.0. Mitsue-Links Internship. June - 2018

# **Cultural Education**

Colombian-Japanese Association Cali, Colombia 2010-2012. Karate Do Goju Ryu Kenshokai, Colombia 2010-2011. Archery Team Icesi University 2013-2014. Rock Group Icesi University (Singer) 2013-2015. Hip Hop Group Icesi University, Colombia 2014-2015. Tenrikyo Church Japanese Language Colombia 2015-2016.

# Work Experience

Mitsue-Links Co. Ltd. - April 2018 - June 2018

User Experience Research Intern

User Tests, Project Reports, Blog Writings, Finding of Cultural Differences.

IOL Colombia - July 2015 - July 2017

Responsible for Logo creating, Web Design, Web development, Brand Marketing.Community Manager - Social Managing. Contacted and interacted with customers, provided customer support. Javier Valencia Garzón, (+52) 3006180477, javiervalenciag@hotmail.com

#### **Audiovisual Children Project 2014**

Responsible for logo and brochure diagramming and creation. Ph. Yamile Sandoval Romero, Santiago de Cali University, Colombia. yamilesandovalr@gmail.com

#### **Doctoral Thesis Cover Page September 2015**

Responsible for cover page diagramming and creation. Ph. Yamile Sandoval Romero, Huelva University, Spain.

#### **Doctoral Final Poster and Thesis Cover Page September 2016**

Responsible for poster and cover page diagramming and creation.

Ph. Damian Mendoza Zambrano, Huelva University, Sevilla University, Malaga University, Cádiz University, Spain. damiamendoza@gmail.com

#### FrutyJoy Logo and Flyer creation May 2017

Responsible for logo and Flyer creation.

Amanda García, FrutyJoy Manager. frutyjoy@gmail.com